Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
The Sand Shadow
Episode 16
Weslie are you okay?
That person is too awesome
We must rescue her
But we can’t deal with them with our ability.
ability
I have successfully copied their ability
It is indeed my invention
So awesome
Then let’s catch up with that person quickly
and bring Xiao Mei back
I can’t walk in this kind of weather and environment.
Me too
Looks like we need a vehicle
Desert Night Paradise
The grand prize is a car
It’s so prosperous here
Is this your first time here?
Welcome to our Desert Night Paradise
Any transaction can be done here
what do you need
we need a vehicle
I have vehicles
The truck known as the “Little Tyrant of Transportation”
The moped known as the “Ship of the Desert”
Which one do you want?
How do you sell your vehicles?
I will give you the best price
After deducting handling fees,
referral fees, and cleaning fees,
100 bottles of water in exchange for one.
What? 100 bottles of water?
I’ll give you another discount. How many bottles of water do you have?
we have so much
So little is not enough
but
You can go there first to play games and win prizes
The final prize is a vehicle
We are good at playing games
let’s go
The water is gone
There’s the arena in front
I heard that you can participate as long as you have the equipment.
And the winner will also get a luxury car
Qualified
next person
Not qualified, no equipment
Wait
Why is this not considered equipment?
Wolffy
next person
Isn’t this Sand Shadow?
It’s Blue Scarf
Everyone, calm down and watch carefully.
He doesn’t have a scarf, it’s not Blue Scarf
That’s right, he’s not Blue Scarf
You can participate
Is this Sand Shadow so powerful?
Big Sister, please let me go.
Big Sister, it’s okay if you don’t let me go
Then can you go back and help me get my doll?
I wouldn’t be able to sleep without it
Welcome, everyone, to the live venue
to watch the Ultimate Battle: The Next Generation 3.0 game!
Now, please welcome our contestants.
Come on Weslie
We need to get the car quickly
The rules of the competition are simple
You can use any method to eliminate your opponents
The last person standing in the arena wins
now I declare
The game starts
Why is it him?
I’m determined to be the champion this time
Stop crying. Crying can easily cause unnecessary trouble.
I don’t want to either
But I’m scared without the doll
don’t talk
It’s strange. I clearly saw there was light here just now.
Did I see it wrong?
let’s go and see
Leave here
Just leave if you say?
Boss Isn’t that Sand Shadow?
Is she the one
The number one master
Blue Scarf
Blue Scarf’s whereabouts are strange
How could it be possible for us to meet her?
It must be fake
Heroine
Forgive us, we know we were wrong
This is our treasure. I give it to you to apologize.
Leave
yes
Get it
stop crying
This is not my doll
but
Thank you
After fierce competition, these players are the only ones left.
It’s time to add some highlights
We will put something into the field to stimulate the game.
As for what to put in?
The choice is yours.
I want to put in a monster.
Okay, let’s add one more monster.
Monster Monster
I’ll cast another monster.
We also choose monster.
Watch me.
Eliminated.
The monster knocked down many contestants at once.
No. 3 and No. 99 are the only ones left on the field.
Why am I so hungry suddenly?
Oops, I forgot that my invention consumes energy.
What should I do?
Congratulations to contestant No. 3 for receiving the materials provided by the audience.
The right to use the laser ray cannon once
Got it
I’m going to drop off food for No. 99 Weslie
No problem. Please pay two bottles of water first.
We will immediately put supplies into the hands of No. 99 for you
two bottles of water
It’s this wild boar again. He uses sneak attacks every time.
Who will help me defeat him?
That’s Slowy
This is a private box. What do you want to do?
I’m looking for Slowy here
you know me
Of course everyone knows your name
I am here this time to recommend a player with great potential to you.
who is
Weslie No. 99
Weslie
Looks a bit weak
But I don’t know why I like him quite a lot.
I’ll vote for him this time
Congratulations to contestant No. 99 for winning the food provided by the audience
An excellent contestant must first know how to hide himself
I have no intention of losing
Weslie
To be continued